

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Dulranga Dhawanitha

- ✓ dulranga.webdesign@gmail.com
- O 'Samaragiri', Waralathpitiya, Polgampola.
- www.dulranga.ml
- +94 74 064 6688

Profile

Front end web developer with 3+ years of experience in Web Development. Skilled at HTML, CSS, JavaScript and other Front end frameworks (eg:- ReactJS). Highly talented at Design to Development with Pure CSS coding. I can build any kind of design to exact development with fully functionality.

Education

2008 - 2021 (current) Royal College, Colombo 07

A/Ls in Mathematics 2023

Employment

2020 – 2021 UI designer and Front end developer at Termux Tricks

Developed and Designed the front end (functionality, animations, design, transitions) of a CTF challenging Platform named Termux-tricks and did Hosting.

2021- current Front end developer at SpicyGaming

Developed exact design provided with UI file. Done custom animations and transitions. The web app created with React JS

Courses

- ► Solo Learn
- Solo Learn
- ► Solo Learn

 RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN
- Solo Learn
 REACT JS

Skills	
HTML	Exper
CSS	Exper
React JS	Exper
JavaScript	Proficien
РНР	Proficien
MySQL	Proficien
3D Developing	Novice
Languages	
Sinhala	
English	

Hindi